IBT0060
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters Benefits Department Records
1966-2002
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0060
18 Cubic Feet 18 record center cartons
This collection consists of Summary Plan Descriptions (SPDs) which are printed booklets distributed to local or group members to explain the benefits covered under local or multi-employer contracts.
General
skeletal bib 14557706 MMS ID# 99145577063604107
Arrangement
This collection is arranged by individual Summary Plan Description.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was transferred to the Teamsters Labor HIsotry Research Center from the IBT.
- Benefits Department Records-Summary Plan Descriptions, 1944-2000; Series 1; This collection consists of summary plan descriptions (SPDs) for regional and/or local union organizations of the IBT. SPDs generally spell out the condiditons of coverage and the details of various benefits - life insurance, accidental death and dismemberment, weekly accident and sickness, etc. The SPDs collected here were negotated at the local or regional level. These rfepresent record copies maintained by the IBT Benefits Department.
  Scope and Contents
  These SPD's spell out the details of benefits coverage for local and/or reginal IBT union organizations.
  Arrangement
  Collection: IBT Benefits Department records Organized into one series: Summary Plan Descriptions The SPDs are arranged individually and labeled as to local or regional union organization.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This collection is open for research.
  - New England Conference Group Plan, 1950; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Pray and Sons Employee's Insurance Plan, 1944; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Local 25 Health and Welfare Fund, 1958; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - New England Trucking Pensions Plan, 1963; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Affiliates Pension Plan, N.D; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anheuser-Busch Group Insurance Plan, 1947; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Anheuser-Busch Retirement Income Plan, N.D; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Anheuser-Busch Purchase and Savings Plan, 1978; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local 744 6th Annual Report for 1958, 1959; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Local 744 Pension Plan, N.D.; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Local 744 Pensions Fund, 1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Local 744 Pensions Fund, 1953; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Local 744 Group Insurance Benefits, 1953; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Local 744 Group Insurance Benefits, 1968; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Brewery Workers Pension Plan, 1964; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Brewery Workers Basic Pension Plan, 1970; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Local 744 Group Insurance Benefits, 1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Central States Pension Plan, 1980; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Central States Annual Returns, 1998; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Central States Trust Agreement, 2000; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Central States Proposed Coverage, 2000; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Central States Benefit Plan A, N.D.; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Central States Active Plan Document, 1999; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Western Conference Plan AD, N.D.; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Western Conference Plan CC, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Western Conference Vision Plan, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Western Conference Plan G-N, 2000; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Oregon vision Care Plan, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Western Conference Dental Plan E, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Western Conference Vision Care Plan, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Western Conference Dental Plan C, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Western Conference Dental Plan D, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Joint Council 42 Prescription Program, 2000; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Western Conference Disability Plan, 1993; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Western Conference Plans GO and GN, 1999; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Washington Construction Welfare Plan, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Western Conference Pension Plan, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Washington Welfare Trust Plan WT, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Washington Welfare Trust Plan JC, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Washington Welfare Trust Plan JC, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Washington Welfare Trust Plan JC, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Washington Welfare Trust Dental Plan, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Joint Council 42 Dental Plan, 1996; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Joint Council 42 Benefit Plan, 1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Oregon Dental Benefit Plan, 1985; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Oregon Medical Benefit Plan, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Washington Welfare Trust Plan 103, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Oregon Benefit Plans C/CW, 1985; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Oregon Benefit Plans F/FW, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Western Conference Pension Plan Comparison, 2000; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Western Conference Health Plan, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Western Conference Health Plan, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Western Conference Pension Plan, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Western Conference Pension Plan, 1992; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Central Pennsylvania Pension Fund Plan, 1969; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Local Union 478 Welfare Fund Plan, 1969; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Washington, DC Motor Truck Employees Pension Plan, 1965; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Central States Pension Plan, 1967; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Local Union 445 Dental and Vision Plan, 1968; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Joint Council 84 Pension Plan, 1968; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Local Union 707 Pension Plan, 1969; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Local Union 707 Welfare Plan, 1968-1969; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Local Union 807 Welfare Plan, 1968; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Teamsters Joint Council No. 83 of Virginia, NA; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Central States, Southeast and Southwest Areas Health and Welfare Fund, 2000; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Miscellanous Security Trust Fund, May 1, 1999; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - PSDS, June 30, 1972; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Affiliates Pension Plan, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - PSDs, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Teamsters-National 401 (k) Savings Plan, 1998; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Teamwork Magazine, 2002; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Teamsters Affiliates Pension Fund, 1966; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Teamsters Affiliates Pension Fund, 1972; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Teamsters Affiliates, ND; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Teamsters Joint Counil No. 16, 1967; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Teamsters Joint Counil No. 16, July 971; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Local 617, 2001-2007 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Local 194, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Local 175 and Local 505 Joint Council 84, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Local 251, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Dairy Industry Philadelphia and Vicinity, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Local 27, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Local 282, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Central Pennsylvania, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Local 463, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Local 348, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Central States, Southeast and Southwest Areas, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Local 435, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Local 557, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Local 703, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Local 992, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Graphics Communications Conference, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Local 705, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Local 401, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Local 33, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Local 346, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Local 377, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Local 705, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Local 331, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Western Conference, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Local 401, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Joint Council 84, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Local 738, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Local 355, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Local 25, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Local 14 and Local 995, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Ohio Contractors Association, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Local 959, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Local 677, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Local 723, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Local 744, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Local 264, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Retiree's Welfare Trust, 2003-2006 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Southwestern Pennsylvania and Western Maryland, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Pension Fund of Maryland, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Local 705, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Local 804, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Local 428, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Local 177, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Hawaii, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Central Pennsylvania, 1987-1999 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Cumberland, Maryland, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Brewery and Related Workers, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Local 395, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Local 194, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Local 408, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Local 277, 0 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Local 346, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Local 714, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Local 20, 1992-1996 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Local 688, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Local 277, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Local 331, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Local 35, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - A&P Shopwell, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Local 70, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Joint Council 42, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Illinois Conference, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Local 575, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Local 575, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Construction, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Minneapolis Food Industry, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Inland Empire, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Local 205, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Local 744, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Local 485, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Automobile Transporters Fund of New York, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Local 638, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Local 856, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Local 688, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Medicare Trust, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Managed Plan, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Local 142, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Local 52, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Local 282, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Local 738, 1995-2002 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Local 705, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Local 804, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Local 707, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Local 781, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Minnesota Construction Division, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Local 802, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Western Pennsylvania, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Southern Region of Teamsters, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Graphics Communications National, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Local 813, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Local 707 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Local 175 and Local 505, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - East Bay Drayage Drivers, 1993-1998 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Central States, Southwestern and Southeastern Areas, 2005-2006 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Central Pennsylvania, 2003-2005 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Local 33, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Local 194, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Cumberland, Maryland, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Local 557, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Local 282, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Local 277, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Local 959, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Local 456, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Western Pennsylvania, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Western Pennsylvania, 2001-2004 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Local 20, 1999-2005 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Local 469, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Local 35, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Minnesota, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - New York, 2007-2010 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Local 52, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Local 422, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Local 813, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Local 716, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Local 830, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Western Pennsylvania, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Milwaukee Drivers, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Local 773, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Local 25, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Local 830, ND (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Managed Health Care Trust Fund, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Washington Teamsters Welfare Trust, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Washington Teamsters Welfare Trust, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Local 617, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Utah-Idaho Teamsters Security Fund, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Washington Teamsters Welfare Trust, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Local 493, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Local 1035, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Local 404, ND (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Utah A.G.C., 2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Utah A.G.C., 1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Utah A.G.C., 1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Industrial Security Fund (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Local 20, 1999-2005 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Local 617, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Local 707, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Retiree's Welfare Trust, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Local 377, ND (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Local 714, ND (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 1998-2005 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - South Bay Teamsters, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Health A Welfare Trust Fund, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Health A Welfare Trust Fund, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Southern California Bakery Driver Trust Fund, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - San Diego County Teamsters Employee Fund, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Health Welfare Benefits Booklet, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Teamster Benefit Trust, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Teamster Benefit Trust, 1997-2002 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 1989-2005 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Local 463 and Local 676, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Local 617, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Utah-Idaho Teamsters, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Utah-Idaho Teamsters, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Utah-Idaho Teamsters, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Utah-Idaho Teamsters, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Central Pennsylvania Teamsters, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Local 617, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Local 727, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Local 727, ND (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Local 814, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Local 377, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Local 617, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Local 617, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 2004-2007 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 2000-2007 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 2003-2007 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 2005-2007 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Local 600, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 2005-2007 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 2005-2007 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 2005-2007 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, ND (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, ND (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Teamsters Benefits Trust, 2004-2007 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 2004-2007 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 2004-2007 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Teamsters Benefit Trust, 2004-2007 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Teamsters Security Fund for Southern Nevada, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Teamsters Security, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Teamsters Care, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Union 25 Health Services, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Utah A.G.C.-Teamsters Welfare Trust, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Utah A.G.C.-Teamsters Welfare Trust, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Utah A.G.C.-Teamsters Welfare Trust, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Utah A.G.C.-Teamsters Welfare Trust, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Utah A.G.C.-Teamsters Welfare Trust, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Utah A.G.C.-Teamsters Welfare Trust, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Local 730, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Local 730, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Local 456, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Local 294, ND (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Local 294, ND (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Local 294, ND (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Local 294, ND (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Local 294, ND (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Local 294, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Local 738, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Local 142, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Local 814, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Local 175 and Local 505 Joint Council 84, 1997-2004 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Benefits Trust, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Teamsters Benefits Trust, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Teamsters Benefits Trust, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Local 142, 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - San Diego County Teamsters, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Local 251, ND (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Teamsters Benefits Trust, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Teamsters Benefits Trust, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Teamsters Benefits Trust, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Local 813, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - New England Teamsters and Baking Industry, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Ohio Conference of Teamsters, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Ohio Conference of Teamsters, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Ohio Conference, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Ohio Conference, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Local 142, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Local 52, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Local 377, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Local 830, ND (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Local 35, 1997-2006 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Local 282, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Local 134, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Local 194, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Local 773, ND (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Automobile Transporters Welfare Fund New York, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Local 331, 2001-2006 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Local 856, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - East Bay Drayage Drivers Security Fund, 1993-1998 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Local 175 and 505 - Joint Council 84, 1994-2004 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Local 705, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Health Fund 917, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Health Fund 917, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Health Fund 917, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Health Fund 917, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Health Fund 917, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Health Fund 917, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Local 282, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Local 802, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Local 142, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Local 142, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Standard Valuations Inc Negotiated Pension Plan, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - A Complete Guide To Your Pension Plan, ND (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Local 813, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Local 682, ND (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Local 783, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Local 27, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Minnesota Teamsters Construction Division, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Automobile Transporters Fund of New York (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Retiree's Welfare Trust, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Local 35, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Local 97, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Local 282, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Local 688, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Local 707, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Local 1205, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Pension Fund of Maryland (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Local 813, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Local 575, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Local 600, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Local 27, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Local 1034, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Local 813, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Local 992, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Cleveland Bakers and Teamsters, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Houston Area, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Local 804, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Local 705, 2000-2003 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Local 714, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Local 210, 2006-2008 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Local 27, 2004-2007 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Local 1205, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Health Fund 917, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Southern Region, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - New York State Conference, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Western Pennsylvania Teamsters, 2004-2007 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Western Pennsylvania Teamsters, 2001-2007 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Inland Empire, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Local 463 and Local 676, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Minnesota Teamsters, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Local 701, ND (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Local 804, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Local 868, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Local 854, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Local 688, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Local 917, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Oregon Processors, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Oregon Processors, 1989-2005 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Oregon Processors, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Local 331, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Local 730, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Local 854, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Local 418, 1994-2005 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Pacific Coast, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Teamsters Life Insurance Trust Fund, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Local 738, ND (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Local 251, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Local 422, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Milwaukee Drivers, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Local 705, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Local 716, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Local 837, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Local 35, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Local 73, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Western Conference, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Western Conference, 1998-2003 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Local 331, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Local 863, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Western Pennsylvania, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Central, Southeast, and Southwest Areas, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Local 917, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Local 868, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Local 1205, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Central, Southeast, and Southwest Areas (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Milwaukee Drivers, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Minnesota Teamsters, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Local 639, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Local 705, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Milwaukee Drivers, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Local 813 and Local 1034, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Local 1034, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Local 814, ND (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Minneapolis Food Distributing Industry, 2004; ` (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Local 27, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Local 463 and Local 676, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Local 485, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Local 705, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Local 744, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Local 194, ND (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Alaska Teamster-Employer Welfare Trust, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Local 707, ND (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Local 730, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Local 282, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Philadelphia Vicinity and Dairy Industry, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Local 395, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Minneapolis Food Distributing Industry, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Chicago, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Local 744, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Local 395, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Local 730, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Western Conference, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Western Conference, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Local 676, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Local 134, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Local 705, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Local 617, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Local 707, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Local 816, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Automobile Transporters Welfare Fund of New York, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Local 311, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Local 33, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Bakery Drivers Local 194, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Central Pennsylvania Teamsters Health and Welfare Fund, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Central Pennsylvania Teamsters, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Central Pennsylvania Teamsters, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 7)